welcome to manulife online access
this step-by-step guide will help you to
activate
and log in to your manulife online
access account
start by visiting our website you can do
this by googling bell financial
or you can simply type our address into
the browser's address bar
www.bellfinancial.ca
once you're on our homepage click client
login
located in the top right corner there
are four different
access points for clients the first is
the manulife online access
that we're going to set up today the
second
is the online access for clients that
only hold segregated funds
such as gif investment plus gif income
plus
and gif encore the third is the manulife
bank
access point and the fourth is the old
version
of client access today we're going to
set up your manulife online access
so click there if you've set up your
manulife online access account
previously
here's where you can sign in using your
email address and password
if you're new to the site click the
button below haven't signed in before
that says let's get you set up if you're
unsure
click let's get you set up and enter
your email address
the system will confirm if you've
already set up an account
to start the setup process you will need
to fill in this form with your name
date of birth and email address
then scroll down and choose a username
you can create a unique username of your
choosing
or you can use your email address next
scroll further and create a secure
password for your account
and then click continue now an email has
been sent to the email address you
provided
open your email account to find that
email from manulife online access
click the link within the email to
continue the setup
you have 15 minutes to complete this
step
once you've followed the email link back
to your account setup
you will be prompted to add a phone
number to your account
enter in your phone number and click add
number
a text message will immediately be sent
to the phone number you provided with a
verification code
enter your code and click continue this
adds
another layer of protection to your
account click continue once again
now it's time to connect your manulife
products enter
your postal code and click find my
products
you will now enter your manulife online
access dashboard
click the gray box that says click here
to activate your manulife securities
account
you will now be prompted for your
account number and the last
four digits of your social security
number you can find your account number
at the top right corner of your manulife
securities statement
it should start with an n or a b if
you're having trouble locating it
call our office at 905-713-3765
our staff will happily assist you
click continue and you'll be asked to
agree to the terms and conditions
once you agree your securities portfolio
information
should appear return to the home screen
by clicking home
and follow the same steps to connect
your investment management account
once your accounts are connected return
to your home screen
scroll down to make a difference go
paperless
click update your preferences
here you can choose whether you'd like
online delivery for all your documents
or you would like your documents
delivered by mail
you can also choose a third option which
allows you to select which documents
you'd like delivered online
and which you'd like to come hard copy
to your address
select the option you would like agree
to the terms of service
and click update my preferences once you
have done this you can scroll up to the
top of the page and click
the back button which will navigate you
back to the dashboard of your manulife
online access account
you can change these preferences anytime
by navigating to the profile tab
on the top right corner of your screen
and clicking
preferences note even if you choose to
have paper documents sent to your
address
all the documents will be saved to the
documents tab
which is also located in your profile
tab at the top right corner of your
screen
when your documents become available you
will be emailed
then you will log into this portal to
find them under your documents tab here
in the profile tab you can navigate to
your dashboard which is your home screen
you can change your preferences and you
can also view all your documents
this is also where you'll go to sign out
we hope that this step-by-step guide has
helped you to activate your account
log in and change your preferences if
you need
any additional assistance please call us
at 905-713-3700